linkfromblog.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy - LinkFromBlog - buy blog reviews, advertise on blogs

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to help you understand generally what information LinkFromBlog collect, steps we take to protect and secure it, how we use and share the information, and finally, how you can access that information or contact us with questions or concerns about the LinkFromBlog web site on which this Privacy Policy is posted (the "Site").  

The Site is intended for individuals 18 years of age or older. By using or accessing the Site, you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years of age. If you are not at least 18 years of age or do not agree with the terms of this Agreement, do not use or access the Site.  

Information you share with LinkFromBlog is used for its internal business purposes. LinkFromBlog does not sell information about you. 

**Information We Collect.**  

LinkFromBlog collects personal information provided by you when you register with us, use the products or services available on the LinkFromBlog Site (the "Service").

LinkFromBlog may also collect personal information provided by you when you enter any promotions offered on the LinkFromBlog site. 

LinkFromBlog may aggregate your information with information from other users (without personally identifying you) and share it with our business partners or others. 

LinkFromBlog may also collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. This information might include information necessary to process payments due to us from you such as your Paypal account email. 

LinkFromBlog automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.   

**Offensive Content**

You may not publish or transmit via LinkFromBlog's service any content that LinkFromBlog reasonably believes:

  * constitutes child pornography;
  * constitutes pornography;
  * is excessively violent, incites violence, threatens violence, or contains harassing content or hate speech;
  * is unfair or deceptive under the consumer protection laws of any jurisdiction, including chain letters and pyramid schemes;
  * is defamatory or violates a person's privacy;
  * creates a risk to a person's safety or health, creates a risk to public safety or health, compromises national security, or interferes with a investigation by law enforcement;
  * improperly exposes trade secrets or other confidential or proprietary information of another person;
  * is intended to assist others in defeating technical copyright protections;
  * clearly infringes on another person's trade or service mark, patent, or other property right;
  * promotes illegal drugs, violates export control laws, relates to illegal gambling, or illegal arms trafficking;
  * is otherwise illegal or solicits conduct that is illegal under laws applicable to you or to LinkFromBlog; or
  * is otherwise malicious, fraudulent, or may result in retaliation against LinkFromBlog by offended viewers.

Content "published or transmitted" via LinkFromBlog's service includes Web content, e-mail, bulletin board postings, chat, and any other type of posting or transmission that relies on any Internet service provided by LinkFromBlog.

**How we use IP Address Information.**  

LinkFromBlog may occasionally get IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our web site. IP addresses, browser and session information may be used for various purposes, including to:

Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP. 

Estimate the total number of users visiting LinkFromBlog from specific geographical regions. 

Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services or resources that we offer. 

Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse. 

Deliver more relevant content to you. 

LinkFromBlog not display or share your IP address to third parties.   

How we use Cookies.  

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set, however, if you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use LinkFromBlog products or services that require you to "sign in" and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings on the LinkFromBlog site.

LinkFromBlog uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

Require you to re-enter your LinkFromBlog password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using LinkFromBlog services.

Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

Conduct research to improve LinkFromBlog content and services.  

**How we Use, Share and Disclose Information We Collect.**  

LinkFromBlog does not share your personal information with others except as described in this policy. We do not share your information with unrelated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. However, LinkFromBlog may display targeted content based on personally non-identifiable information (such as browser type and IP address) and/or personal selection.

LinkFromBlog may use your personal information where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction, to operate or improve LinkFromBlog and related products and services, to do something that you have asked us to do, or tell you of products and services that we think may be of interest.

LinkFromBlog may use your email address to contact you with required email messages about the Service.

Where you are contacted with an offer or service based on information you have shared with LinkFromBlog, we will do our best to provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving such further communications at the time you are contacted. 

LinkFromBlog does or may share personally identifiable information about you under the following circumstances:

In the course of operating our business, it may be necessary or appropriate for us to provide access to your personal information to others such as our service providers, contractors and select vendors so that we can operate the Service and our business. Where practical, we seek to obtain confidentiality agreements that are consistent with this policy and that limit others' use or disclosure of the information you have shared.

We may transfer personal information to certain advertising partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

We may share your personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, if in our judgment, disclosure is required or appropriate in such circumstances.

We may share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of LinkFromBlog terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

As we continue to develop our business, we might also sell all or part of our business. In such transactions, personally identifiable information you have shared with us is generally one of the business assets that may be transferred. The transferred personally identifiable information will remain subject to the promises made in this privacy policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.  

If there is ever a change to how LinkFromBlog uses or intends to use personal information, we will post that change to this policy and, if the new policy is materially less restrictive than this policy, we will seek your consent.  

**Confidentiality and Security.**  

No data transmissions over the Internet or via wireless networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make efforts to ensure security on our systems.

We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

Your LinkFromBlog Account Information is password-protected.

In certain areas, LinkFromBlog uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.  

If LinkFromBlog learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps, however, we will never ask you to submit additional personal information or to verify the status of or information related to your account in any electronic communication email. By using this web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. LinkFromBlog may post a notice on our web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the LinkFromBlog.com web site. LinkFromBlog may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances, however, we will never ask you to submit additional personal information or to verify the status of or information related to your account in any such email. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [privacy@linkfromblog.com](mailto:privacy@linkfromblog.com).  

**Changing your Preferences and Personal Information.**  

You can edit your LinkFromBlog Account Information at any time. You can delete your LinkFromBlog account by visiting our Account Deletion page; however, please note that some personal information, primarily your contact information, may remain in LinkFromBlog's records to the extent necessary to protect LinkFromBlog's legal interests or document compliance with regulatory requirements.  

**Contacting LinkFromBlog.**  

If you have a privacy concern regarding LinkFromBlog, or this policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of this web site, you should then write to us by email to [privacy@linkfromblog.com](mailto:privacy@linkfromblog.com).  

If you object to any sharing of your personal information that may be permitted under this policy, you may do so by writing us at the above address. We will take reasonable steps to accommodate your requests as they relate to our practices. In some instances, honoring your requests may interfere with or preclude your ability to use the Service or may require us to terminate our relationship with you.
